https://www.hawkinsspeedshop.com/privacy.html

Browse Store
Internet Specials2005-2011 Ford Mustang4x4 Accessories and EquipmentBrake SystemsCarburetors and Fuel PumpsChrome and Billet AccessoriesCooling SystemDriveline ComponentsECM TunersExhaust HeadersFlexplates and Transmission ShieldsFord Performance PartsFuel Cells and Fuel JugsFuel InjectionHeat Protection ProductsHigh Output Alternators and StartersHood Scoops, Hoods, & Body PartsIgnition Systems and PartsIntake ManifoldsLS1 Performance PartsLubricants and ChemicalsNitrous Oxide KitsPerformance Engine Parts and Related ToolsPerformance Mufflers & Exhaust SystemsPerformance PlumbingPerformance ShiftersRacing Chassis ComponentsRacing Electronics and AidsRacing Safety EquipmentRacing Tires, Racing Wheels, and AccessoriesRacing ToolsRacing Transmission PartsRust RemoverSteering System ComponentsSuperChargersTachometers and Auto GaugesTripleX Race CompanyTurbos
HomePrivacyPrivacy Policy
Hawkins Speed Shop is committed to ensuring user privacy in our products and services. Our privacy and security policy was developed to offer the highest-quality services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with customers and visitors to our web site. This policy is designed to give you a better understanding in how we collect, use and safeguard all personal information provided to us.
Hawkins Speed Shop encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all Web sites you visit.
What Information Do We Collect?
When you visit our web site you may provide us with personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis. Web site use information is also collected as you and others browse our web site.
Personal Information Collected
Hawkins Speed Shop is the sole owner of the information collected on this web site. We will not sell, share, or in any way disclose this information to others without your consent. You will provide us personal information about yourself, your firm or company, and your practices when you register through our web site e-commerce shopping cart SEO-Cart.
If you choose to purchase products or services from us, you may need to give personal information and authorization to successfully complete your purchase. The e-commerce shopping cart software SEO-Cart order forms request this data from users including: billing and shipping contact information including but not limited to customer name, addresses, phone numbers and e-mail addresses; financial information depending on payment method. Credit card payments require credit card number, card code and expiration date. E-check payments require bank name, routing number and account number. These orders may require other billing contact information including but not limited to billing name, billing phone number, and company name. This information is used for billing purposes and may be used to verify and fill customers’ orders. If a difficulty is encountered when processing an order, your billing or shipping contact information may be used for obvious purposes.
Security
Hawkins Speed Shop has implemented multiple levels of web site security to ensure a safe online shopping environment. We use secure servers that are monitored 24/7 and have received SSL secure server certification. To date, Hawkins Speed Shop has not received any reports of credit card fraud.
All personal information, billing information, and all other transaction information are required to be collected from at least a 128-bit encrypted secure web page. Upon order submission all information is serialized and securely stored in a database for our customers’ protection. Fraudulent order information is subject to be disclosed to your credit card issuing bank.
Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, Hawkins Speed Shop will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. We will cover this liability only if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made at hawkinsspeedshop.com while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.
Cookies
Cookies provide a means for a Web server to induce a computer to store information about itself which can subsequently be called up by the Web server when required. Currently, our only use of cookies is to store a unique session identifier, which allows us to maintain products added to your shopping cart and to differentiate you from other shoppers so your shopping cart is only available to you. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not store any personal information that you provide to us in your cookies.
IP Addresses
Your IP address is an identifier for your computer or device on a TCP/IP network, in this case, the Internet. Your IP address is automatically collected by our web server to analyze trends, administer the site, and track user movement. Your IP address is stored when you place an order and may be used in fraudulent charge investigations.
3rd Party Services
We may use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services that they may choose to purchase. These companies do not share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
Legal Disclaimer
We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our web site.
Linked Web Sites
We provide links to third-party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third-party sites.
Children’s Privacy
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. Hawkins Speed Shop encourages parents to go online with their children.
Accessing and Updating Information
We need your help in making sure your personal information is correct in our systems. Please notify us of changes to your name, address, title, phone number or e-mail address by Telephone 1-800-443-7748 or via our contact form.
Your Consent
You consent to our collection and use of your personal information described in this privacy and security policy by using our web site. We will post any changes made to our privacy policy and procedures on our web site which will be accessible to you.
Contact Us
If you have questions regarding this privacy policy, procedures and practices carried out by Hawkins Speed Shop, or your dealings with our web site or shopping cart software SEO-Cart, please contact us at: Hawkins Speed Shop, 116 SW 1st Street, Richmond, Indiana 47374. Telephone1-800-443-7748 or via our contact form.
Modification
Modification of our privacy and security policy performed by Cirkuit Networks, Inc. Hawkins Speed Shop reserves the right to change or update this policy at any time by posting a notice that we are changing our Privacy & Security Policy.
Mailing List
Sign up for our newsletter:
Unsubscribe
Contact Us
Hawkins Speed Shop
116 SW 1st Street
Richmond,IN Toll Free: 1.800.443.7748Local: 765.962.4927Contact Us
Hours of Operation:
Mon-Fri, 8:30 a.m.-5:30 p.m.
Saturday, 8:30 a.m.-12:00 p.m.
Company
Contact UsChassis ShopAbout UsLocationGallerySitemapOrdering and ReturnsPrivacy
Popular Categories
Internet Specials2005-2011 Ford Mustang4x4 Accessories and EquipmentBrake SystemsCarburetors and Fuel PumpsChrome and Billet AccessoriesCooling SystemDriveline ComponentsECM TunersExhaust HeadersFlexplates and Transmission ShieldsFord Performance PartsFuel Cells and Fuel JugsFuel InjectionHeat Protection ProductsHigh Output Alternators and Starters
© 1955 - 2020 Hawkins Speed Shop - All Rights Reserved
Ordering, Payment, Shipping and Return Policies
Privacy Policy
Cirkuit: Best Ecommerce Platform
